http://www.pryormarking.com/privacy-policy

SPA
Visit us on Facebook (Opens in a new tab)
Visit us on Twitter (Opens in a new tab)
Visit us on Google Plus (Opens in a new tab)
Visit us on Linkedin (Opens in a new tab)
Visit us on Youtube (Opens in a new tab)
Our Privacy Policy
This policy (together with our terms of website use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which we, Edward Pryor & Son Ltd, trading as Pryor Marking Technology, Egerton Street, Sheffield S1 4JX, will process any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, in the course of using our site www.pryormarking.com. For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 we are the data controller.
Your Information
When you use our site, there are a number of ways in which you provide information and other data to us. By using the site, you consent to us processing and collecting this data, on the terms and for the reasons which are explained below.
How your Information is Used
We may use your information to:
Send you our newsletters from time to time.
Ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
Provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
Carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
Allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
Notify you about changes to our service.
If you do not want us to use your information for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box on the form on which you submit your data. You can also contact us directly at info@pryormarking.com
Please note that if you click on, or follow, any links from our site to external websites, including Social Media networks, our privacy policy will no longer apply. Please check the privacy policies of any such external site before submitting any personal data, as we cannot accept any responsibility or liability in relation to them.
Data Storage
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted by Worldpay
We take your privacy very seriously, and will take all reasonable steps to protect your personal data, but please be aware that any data which you send to our site is sent at your own risk.
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, processed and/or stored at a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
Disclosure of your Information
We may disclose your personal information to any of our group companies (which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 736 of the UK Companies Act 1985) and also to third parties in the following circumstances: -
to any prospective seller or buyer of all (or part of) our business or assets;
If we are required to do so by law, any applicable regulation or to protect the rights, property, or safety of ourselves or others. This may include disclosing to other companies and organisations in connection with fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Access to Inforamtion
You have the right under the Data Protection Act to access the information which we hold about you. If you wish to exercise this right, please send your request to info@pryormarking.com. Please state the subject of the email as “Data Protection Request” to ensure that your request is dealt with promptly.
Back to top
Edward Pryor & Son Ltd
Trading as:
Pryor Marking Technology
Egerton Street
Sheffield
S1 4JX
UK
+44 114 2766044
Company Number: 313230
Registered in England and Wales
Pryor Marking Technology designs and manufactures the widest range of permanent marking systems in the world, together with software and barcode readers for component tracking and tracing.
Follow us online:
Visit us on Facebook (Opens in a new tab)
Visit us on Twitter (Opens in a new tab)
Visit us on Google Plus (Opens in a new tab)
Visit us on Linkedin (Opens in a new tab)
Visit us on Youtube (Opens in a new tab)
© Pryor 2020 All rights reserved. Text, images, graphics, sound, animations and videos on this website are protected by copyright.
Website by Evoluted New Media (Opens in a new tab)
